Text 5: A new professor from Japan arrived at Hogwarts School of Wizardry to teach Defense Against the Dark Arts. Professor Nakamura was young, but strict enough to make all the students fear him and do all their homework. 
One day when Hermione, Harry and Ron were walking down the corridor of the farthest tower of the school, they met a man wearing a large and black hat. The man turned out to be a follower of Voldemort and tried to kill Harry Potter. But suddenly, Professor Nakamura came out of the corner and did battle with the man in the hat. The man in the hat used dirty tricks and knocked the teacher's wand out of his hands and it rolled down the stairs. But the battle didn't end there and despite the fact that Professor Nakamura was left without a magic wand, he used his karate skills and defeated the man in the hat without any magic. After that, Professor Nakamura won the hearts of all the female students at Hogwarts. However, the appearance of the man in the hat was not just ...
